Register of the Citizens Committee for Reorganization of the Executive Branch of the Government Records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Printed Matter, 1947-1958 (Box 74-92)
  - Clippings
    - Transportation, 1953-1956 (Folder 88: 11)
    - United States - Foreign relations, 1951 February (Box-folder 89: 1-2)
    - United States. Department of Defense, 1956-1958 (Folder 89: 3)
    - Vermont, 1957-1958 (Folder 89: 4)
    - Veterans affairs, 1950-1952 (Folder 89: 5)
    - Waste in government spending, 1952 (Folder 89: 6)
    - Water resources and power
      - 1953-1955 (Folder 89: 7)
      - 1956 (Box-folder 90: 1)
  - Publications
    - Issued by the CCREBG
      - General
        - Undated (Folder 90: 2-4)
        - 1949 (Folder 90: 5)
        - 1950 (Folder 90: 6)
        - 1952-1954 (Folder 90: 7)
        - 1955 (Folder 90: 8)
        - 1956 (Folder 90: 9)
        - 1957 (Folder 90: 10)
        - 1958 (Folder 90: 11)
      - Committee Reporter, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 91: 1)
      - Discussion Guide Series on the Hoover Commission Report, n.d. (Folder 91: 2)
      - Reorganization News, 1949-1958 (Folder 91: 3)
      - Reorganization Record, 1949 (Folder 91: 4)
    - Collected by the CCREBG
      - General
        - Undated (Folder 91: 5)
        - 1949 (Folder 91: 6-7)
        - 1950 (Folder 91: 8)
        - 1951 (Folder 91: 9)
        - 1952 (Folder 91: 10)
        - 1954 (Folder 91: 11)
        - 1955 (Folder 91: 12)
        - 1956 (Box-folder 92: 1)
        - 1957 (Folder 92: 2)
      - Taxpayer's Dollar, 1955-1956 (Folder 92: 3)
      - Washington Report, 1955-1956 (Folder 92: 4)
- Motion Picture Films (Film Shelf)
  Access
  The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To view films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
  - "What Price Government?" 16mm film, 700 feet (Film shelf Reel)
  - "Waste Not-Want Not" 16mm film, 1000 feet (Film shelf Reel)